// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q020: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'The company’s construction of a factory in Thailand has ------ in the creation of more than 500 new jobs.',
      choices: ['generated', 'resulted', 'occupied', 'realized'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['resulted'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ install a bus stop on the sidewalk, an application for a building permit must be submitted to the city.',
      choices: ['For', 'On behalf of', 'Additionally', 'In order to'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['In order to'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The newly installed labeling machine can apply stickers to products twice as ------ as the previous one.',
      choices: ['quick', 'quicker', 'quickness', 'quickly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['quickly'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Kwon Market Research conducted ------ research to develop new products for clients in the food industry.',
      choices: ['durable', 'generous', 'dependent', 'extensive'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['extensive'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The Mogen Modern Museum requires that the use of cell phones ------ to designated areas within the museum.',
      choices: ['is limited', 'has limited', 'be limited', 'limit'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['be limited'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'According to today’s newspaper, ------ 3,000 residents, including adults and children, participated in the sporting event yesterday.',
      choices: ['similarly', 'nearly', 'anonymously', 'sufficiently'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['nearly'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Our team is ------ surveying visitors to the event that will be held this weekend at Riverside Park.',
      choices: ['instead of', 'along with', 'in place of', 'in charge of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['in charge of'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Employees who have been assigned to work overseas can receive online ------ to learn the local language.',
      choices: ['tutorials', 'exports', 'permits', 'measurements'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['tutorials'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The number of people working for companies ------ to the automotive industry in that district has increased in recent years.',
      choices: ['relation', 'related', 'relate', 'relates'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['related'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'New employees at Wagner Corporation are invited ------ a welcome party held on the second floor of its headquarters.',
      choices: ['attend', 'attending', 'to attend', 'attended'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['to attend'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}